Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Oh...
♪ 哦...
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he. ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense be
something you wish... ♪
♪ 如果航海方面的废话是
你想要的东西...♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish. ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Ready?
SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 准备好了吗？
海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
[Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
[字幕由THE赞助
美国教育部
[and NICKELODEON]
[和尼克频道]
Here you go, sir.
给你，先生。
A King Size
Ultra Krabby Supreme
with the works
特大号
超级蟹蟹至尊
与作品
double batter-fried on a stick.
双面糊炸在棍子上。
Thanks!
谢谢！
Barnacle head.
藤壶头。
Pardon me?
对不起？
You forgot your mayonnaise.
你忘记带蛋黄酱了。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Look at them eating
that garbage.
看他们吃饭的样子
那个垃圾。
It's disgusting.
那真令人恶心。
They're sickening.
他们真令人作呕。
I hate Krabby Patties.
我讨厌蟹肉饼。
Good one, Squidward!
好样的，章鱼哥！
Good what?
好什么？
Like you don't know.
就像你不知道一样。
Saying "I hate Krabby Patties."
说“我讨厌蟹黄馅饼”。
That's hilarious!
太搞笑了！
Everyone loves Krabby Patties.
每个人都喜欢蟹黄馅饼。
Yeah, well, not me.
是的，好吧，不是我。
You're good at that.
你很擅长这个。
Hey, everyone!
嘿，大家好！
Squid says he doesn't
like Krabby Patties. Ha!
鱿鱼说他没有
像蟹黄饼一样。哈!
Good one, Squidward!
好样的，章鱼哥！
Don't encourage them!
不要鼓励他们！
They'll never leave.
他们永远不会离开。
Sorry, Squidward.
对不起，章鱼哥。
It's just so funny.
真是太有趣了。
You know what we say:
你知道我们说什么：
The only people
who don't like a Krabby Patty
唯一的人
谁不喜欢蟹肉饼
have never tasted one.
从未尝过。
That's me.
这就是我。
Never had one, never will.
从来没有过，也永远不会。
What?
什么？
What did you say?
你说什么？
I've never had a Krabby Patty
我从来没有吃过蟹肉饼
and never will.
并且永远不会。
I'm sorry... I don't...
对不起...我不...
I've never had a Krabby Patty.
我从来没有吃过蟹肉饼。
Those words!
那些话！
Is it possible to use them
可以使用它们吗
in a sentence
together like that?
造句
就这样在一起？
I've never had a Krabby Patty!
我从来没有吃过蟹肉饼！
Never had a Krabby Patty?
从来没有吃过蟹黄饼？
Well, you've gotta have one
right now!
那么，你必须拥有一个
现在！
No wonder you're
always so miserable!
难怪你是
总是这么惨！
Here, try this!
来，试试这个！
Get that garbage outta my face!
把那些垃圾从我脸上拿走！
If you try it, you'll love it!
如果您尝试一下，您一定会喜欢的！
Try one of those radioactive
sludge balls you call food?
尝试其中一种放射性物质
你称之为食物的污泥球？
Next I suppose you'll want me to
go square-dancing with Patrick.
接下来我想你会希望我这样做
和帕特里克一起去跳广场舞。
Sorry, Patrick.
对不起，帕特里克。
Come on, you're gonna...
来吧，你会...
No.
不。
Open up the tunnel.
打开隧道。
Here comes the train.
火车来了。
Choo-choo...
咕咕...
No!
不！
Whoop! What's that
in your ear?
哎哟！那是什么
在你耳边？
Quit it.
戒掉吧。
Come on, open wide!
来吧，敞开心扉！
SpongeBob, if I were trapped
海绵宝宝，如果我被困了
at the bottom of a
well for three years
在 a 的底部
三年了
with nothing to eat
but that Krabby Patty
没有东西吃
但那个蟹蟹帕蒂
I'd eat my own legs first!
我先吃自己的腿！
And not just the extra ones.
不仅仅是额外的。
But it's good for you!
但这对你有好处！
Good for you?
对你有好处？
That thing is a heart attack
on a bun!
那是心脏病发作
在一个小圆面包上！
No, Squidward, I meant...
good for your soul.
不，章鱼哥，我的意思是……
对你的灵魂有好处。
Oh, puh-leez! I have no soul.
哦，噗噗！我没有灵魂。
Okay, just half.
好吧，就一半。
No.
不。
A quarter?
四分之一？
No.
不。
One bite?
一口？
Just smell it.
闻一下就知道了。
If I didn't want it out there
如果我不想让它在那里
what makes you think I'd find it
是什么让你认为我会找到它
more appealing in here?!
这里更有吸引力？！
Come on, Squidward.
来吧，章鱼哥。
No.
不。
One bite.
咬一口。
No.
不。
You won't be sorry.
你不会后悔的。
No!
不！
It's delicious...
真好吃...
SpongeBob, how long are you
prepared to keep this up?
海绵宝宝，你还有多久
准备好继续这样下去了吗？
Give me that!
给我那个！
When I die... you stay
away from my funeral.
当我死后...你留下来
远离我的葬礼。
Ohh... do I really...
哦...我真的...
Ah...
啊...
Ooh...
哦...
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh...
噢噢噢噢...
Why... this Krabby Patty
may be the most...
为什么……这个蟹肉饼
可能是最...
Horrible!
可怕！
Putrid!
腐烂！
Poorly prepared!
Vile!
准备不充分！
卑鄙！
Unappetizing!
没有胃口！
Disgusting excuse for a sandwich
三明治的恶心借口
it has ever been my displeasure
这一直是我的不满
to have slither down my throat!
滑进我的喉咙！
But..
但..
And I curse this Krabby Patty
我诅咒这个蟹黄派蒂
and all who enjoy them
to an early
以及所有喜欢它们的人
到早
and well-deserved grave!
当之无愧的坟墓！
Get it?
得到它？
But it doesn't make any sense
但这没有任何意义
The Krabby Patty
is an absolute good.
蟹肉饼
是绝对的好。
Nobody is immune
to its tasty charms.
没有人能免疫
其美味的魅力。
Nobody but me.
除了我之外没有人。
Are you sure?
你确定吗？
Does this look unsure to you?
这对你来说看起来不确定吗？
No.
不。
Good!
好的！
Now go spread the word.
现在就去宣传吧。
Come on! Come on!
快点！快点！
Ah...
啊...
Still alive!
还活着！
Oh, so delicious!
哦，真好吃！
Oh...! The wasted years!
哦...！荒废的岁月！
I got to have more.
I got to have more!
我必须拥有更多。
我必须要更多！
But wait!
但是等等！
After that performance
那次表演之后
he'd never let me live it down!
他永远不会让我失望！
I gotta sneak one, just one...
我得偷偷拿一张，就一张……
then I'm off the stuff for good!
那我就永远摆脱这些东西了！
I didn't think it was possible
我不认为这是可能的
but I guess some people
just don't like Krabby Patties!
但我猜有些人
只是不喜欢蟹肉饼！
Uh, SpongeBob?
呃，海绵宝宝？
Yes, Squidward?
是的，章鱼哥？
I need a Triple Krabby Supreme
on a kelp bun
我需要三重蟹黄至尊
放在海带面包上
with extra sea pickle and,
and burn it to a crisp, okay?
加上额外的海泡菜，
然后把它烧得酥脆，好吗？
Coming right up!
马上就来了！
Listen, Squidward.
听着，章鱼哥。
I want to apologize for before.
我想为之前的事情道歉。
I was only trying
to make you happy.
我只是想尝试
让你开心。
But now I've learned
但现在我已经学会了
there's room for
all kinds of people...
有空间
各种各样的人...
and they don't
all have to like
the same things.
他们不
都必须喜欢
同样的事情。
Don't go.
别走。
While I strongly disagree
虽然我强烈不同意
with your decision, I accept it.
你的决定，我接受。
You know, it's not often
I get to make one like this.
你知道，这样的情况并不常见
我要做一个这样的。
I want to see the look
on their face
我想看看样子
在他们的脸上
when they take that first bite.
当他们咬第一口时。
Triple Krabby Supreme!
三重蟹蟹至尊！
Did somebody order
a Triple Krabby Supreme?
有人订购了吗
三重蟹黄至尊？
Huh? They must have left.
啊？他们一定已经离开了。
Well, uh, why don't you
just uh, leave it out here
嗯，呃，你为什么不呢
只是呃，把它留在这里
in case they come back.
万一他们回来了。
Nope, a patty this special
should be eaten fresh
不，这么特别的肉饼
应该新鲜吃
and... well... I haven't
had one of these babies
而且...好吧...我还没有
有这些婴儿之一
in over 20 minutes so...
20多分钟后...
Well, whoever they were,
they had great taste!
好吧，无论他们是谁，
他们的品味很好！
Mm, mm-hmm-hmm,
mm-hmm-hmm-hmm...
嗯，嗯嗯嗯，
嗯嗯嗯嗯……
Ah, they don't know
what they're missing.
啊，他们不知道
他们缺少什么。
Well, back to work.
好吧，回去工作吧。
What do I have to do?
我必须做什么？
Eat one out of the garbage?
从垃圾堆里吃一个？
I wish I could eat this,
but I'm so darn full.
我希望我能吃这个
但我实在是太饱了。
Oh well.
那好吧。
I had to say garbage...
but okay!
不得不说垃圾...
但好吧！
Bleah...
布莱亚...
Oh no, what's this doing here?
哦不，这是在做什么？
This patty should be cremated!
这个肉饼应该火化！
I know you didn't like him
我知道你不喜欢他
but it means so much
that you came.
但这意义重大
你来了。
Honey?
蜂蜜？
What? Oh...
什么？哦...
I have got to get my hands
on a Krabby Patty!
我必须抓住我的手
在蟹肉饼上！
And no one's going to stop me.
没有人会阻止我。
There it is...
那里是……
Holy shrimp!
圣虾！
I don't know where to start.
我不知道从哪里开始。
All that matters is that
重要的是
it's just you... and me...
and nobody...
只有你...和我...
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Is that you?
那是你吗？
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
Uh, uh, uh...
what are you doing here?
呃呃呃……
你在这里做什么？
I always come to work
at 3:00 a.m.
我总是来上班
凌晨 3:00
This is when I count
the sesame seeds.
这是我数数的时候
芝麻。
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
Uh... I forgot my...
呃……我忘了我的……
And why is the patty vault open?
为什么馅饼金库是开放的？
And why are you holding
a patty behind your back?
你为什么持有
背后有小馅饼吗？
I... I... I...
no, I didn't do...
我...我...我...
不，我没有做...
And why are you
acting so nervous?
而你为什么是
表现得这么紧张？
And why are you
sweating so much?
而你为什么是
出这么多汗？
And why do you look so hungry?
还有你为什么看起来这么饿？
No, wait... it's
not what you think.
不，等等……这是
不是你想的那样。
Th-this is a big
misunderstanding.
Th-这是一个大
误解。
You've got to believe me, I...
你一定要相信我，我...
Listen, I am telling you...
听着，我告诉你……
You better listen
to me, SpongeBob.
你最好听听
对我来说，海绵宝宝。
You like Krabby Patties,
don't you, Squidward?
你喜欢蟹黄饼，
不是吗，章鱼哥？
Yes! Yes! I admit it, SpongeBob!
是的！是的！我承认，海绵宝宝！
I loveKrabby Patties!
我喜欢蟹黄馅饼！
I knew it all along, Squidward.
我一直都知道，章鱼哥。
No one can resist
a Krabby Patty.
无人能抗拒
蟹肉饼。
Squidward!
How many are you eating?
章鱼哥！
你吃几个？
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
Squidward, you can't eat
all those patties at one time!
章鱼哥，你不能吃
一次性所有这些肉饼！
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
What's gonna happen?
会发生什么？
Am I gonna blow up?
我会爆炸吗？
No, worse... it'll go
right to your thighs...
不，更糟的是……它会消失
一直到你的大腿...
My thighs?
我的大腿？
And then you'll blow up.
然后你就会爆炸。
Yeah...
是的...
I remember my first
Krabby Patty.
我记得我的第一次
克拉比·帕蒂。
Excuse me, Miss.
对不起，小姐。
I don't want to have
to report you again.
我不想拥有
再次举报您。
I was just wondering....
我只是想知道......
Is it the "homework pencil"
on the left side of the paper
这是“作业铅笔”吗？
在纸的左侧
next to the "quiz pencil"
在“测验铅笔”旁边
or over on the right side,
all by itself... or...
或者在右侧，
一切都靠它自己……或者……
I think it goes
stuck inside your...
我认为可以
困在你的...
Wait! I got it!
等待！我得到了它！
The "quiz pencil"
goes right over here
“测验铅笔”
就到这里
next to the "essay" pencil.
在“论文”铅笔旁边。
And the "essay" pencil
gets turned sideways
还有“论文”铅笔
被转向一边
towards the notepad.
向记事本。
Just in case
I have to write an essay.
以防万一
我必须写一篇论文。
Good morning, class!
早上好，同学们！
Sorry I'm late...
抱歉我来晚了...
I got caught in traffic
on the way here
我陷入交通堵塞
在来这里的路上
when that whole
"I'm gonna be doing this
for the rest of my life" thing
当整个
“我要做这个
在我的余生中”的事情
reared its ugly head
抬起丑陋的头
and I...
而我...
Anyway, we have a new student
starting today.
无论如何，我们有一个新学生
从今天开始。
So let's all put on a happy face
所以让我们都露出幸福的表情
for Flats the Flounder.
对于平底鲽鱼。
Tell the class something
about yourself, Flats.
告诉全班同学一些事情
关于你自己，弗拉茨。
Well, I like to
kick people's butts.
嗯，我喜欢
踢人们的屁股。
What a card.
多么好的一张卡片啊。
Now, Flats, it's time
to pick your seat.
现在，平底斯，是时候了
选择你的座位。
Just go ahead
and sit anywhere you like.
继续吧
然后坐在你喜欢的任何地方。
Okay, class,
as you remember last week...
好的，上课，
正如你记得上周...
Hi, I'm SpongeBob.
嗨，我是海绵宝宝。
Hi, SpongeBob.
嗨，海绵宝宝。
I'm gonna kick your butt.
我要踢你的屁股。
Whoa!
哇！
That joke was almost
funnier the second time.
那个笑话几乎是
第二次就更搞笑了
No... I mean it.
不……我是说真的。
That time
it almost seemed like...
那个时候
几乎看起来就像...
you did mean it.
你确实是这么想的。
Mrs. Puff.
泡芙女士。
Yes, SpongeBob?
是的，海绵宝宝？
Can I be excused
for the rest of my life?
我可以原谅吗
我的余生？
Why no, SpongeBob.
为什么不呢，海绵宝宝。
I'm in the middle of a coffee-
fueled sermon right now.
我正在喝咖啡-
现在为讲道加油。
You can't afford
to miss this information.
你买不起
错过这个信息。
Yes, Mrs.Puff.
是的，帕夫夫人。
Sorry, Mrs. Puff.
对不起，帕芙女士。
Now... can I please
have a volunteer
现在...我可以吗
有一名志愿者
to come up to the board?
进入董事会？
How about you, Flats?
你呢，弗拉茨？
Please draw for us a diagram
请给我们画个图
of a basic four-way
intersection, Flats.
基本四路的
交叉路口，平地。
Please turn and show the class
请转身给全班同学展示
what you drew, honey.
你画的是什么，亲爱的。
My!
How very creative!
我的！
多么有创意啊！
We have an artist in the class!
我们班上有一位艺术家！
I just don't understand.
我只是不明白。
Why would Flats
want to kick mybutt?
为什么要平底鞋
想踢我的屁股吗？
I haven't said
two words to the guy!
我还没说过
对那家伙说两句话！
Hi, I'm SpongeBob.
嗨，我是海绵宝宝。
One... two...
一……二……
Oh no, that's three!
哦不，是三个！
What am I gonna do?
我要做什么？
What's that?! Someone's coming.
那是什么？有人来了。
They're getting closer.
他们越来越近了。
I just got to act natural.
我只需要表现得自然就好。
Oh, that's real nice.
哦，那真是太好了。
Whew!
I thought for sure
that was gonna be...
哇！
我确信无疑
那将会是...
Flats?!
公寓？！
Uh, hello, um... sir.
呃，你好，嗯……先生。
Uh... kicked any
good butts lately?
呃……踢过任何一个
最近屁股好吗？
Yeah, I remember last week
是的，我记得上周
I was kickin' this
guy's butt real good...
我正在踢这个
这家伙的屁股真好……
and he leans over and says...
他倾身说道……
"Hey, ya know... life's like
a bucket of wood shavings,
“嘿，你知道……生活就像
一桶木屑，
"except for when the shavings
are in a pail...
“除了当刨花
在桶里...
then it's like a pail
of wood shavings."
然后它就像一个桶
木屑。”
Hey, that story
really speaks to me.
嘿，那个故事
真的对我说话。
Really? What's it say?
真的吗？它说什么？
It says now I'm gonna
kick your butt twice as hard.
它说现在我要
加倍用力踢屁股。
It says now I'm gonna
kick your butt twice as hard.
它说现在我要
加倍用力踢屁股。
And I'll leave
Gary's water bowl to Gary
我会离开
加里的水碗给加里
and my curtains to...
还有我的窗帘...
Oh, Neptune,
I just can't do this!
哦，海王星，
我就是做不到！
Death row.
"Next-in-line" speaking.
死囚牢房。
“下一个”讲话。
Hi! I'd like to place
an order for delivery.
你好！我想放置
交货订单。
Patrick! Is that you?
帕特里克！那是你吗？
Yeah. Hey, Mario.
是的。嘿，马里奥。
Let me get a large,
double olive, double...
让我来一个大的，
双橄榄，双...
Patrick, listen!
It's me, SpongeBob!
帕特里克，听着！
是我，海绵宝宝！
I need your help.
我需要你的帮助。
You're working
at Pizza Castle now?
你正在工作
现在在披萨城堡吗？
What? No... listen!
什么？不……听着！
I'm in big trouble.
我有大麻烦了。
There's a new guy at school here
and he wants kick my butt.
学校来了一个新同学
他想踢我的屁股。
Listen, you're big and strong.
听着，你又大又壮。
Do you think
you can come down here...
你认为
你可以到这里来...
maybe rough him up a bit,
just to get him off my back?
也许对他有点粗暴，
只是为了让他离开我的背吗？
Please, Patrick!
拜托，帕特里克！
I'm so scared it feels
like I'm gonna throw up.
我很害怕这种感觉
就像我要吐一样。
No, they're not closed...
不，他们没有关门……
I know, you want olives...
我知道，你想要橄榄...
Patrick? You there?
帕特里克？你在那里？
Oh, I'm sorry, SpongeBob.
哦，对不起，海绵宝宝。
I was just talking
to my old community
college buddy, Flats.
我只是在说话
到我的老社区
大学好友，平底鞋。
I bumped into him
at the soda store,
isn't that funny?
我撞到了他
在汽水店，
这不是很有趣吗？
It must have been years
since we've seen each other.
一定已经很多年了
自从我们见面以来。
Well, let me get going.
好吧，让我走吧。
He's got to go
back to school soon.
他得走了
很快就回学校了。
He says he's got to
kick somebody's butt.
他说他必须
踢某人的屁股。
Aah...!
啊啊……！
Hello?
Is this Pizza Castle?
你好？
这是披萨城堡吗？
Aah...!
啊啊……！
Come in, SpongeBob.
进来吧，海绵宝宝。
Mrs. Puff, can I be
in a different class?
泡芙女士，我可以吗
在不同的班级？
But why?
但为什么？
I can't tell you.
我不能告诉你。
Why ever not?
为什么从来没有？
I just can't, Mrs. Puff.
我就是做不到，帕芙女士。
My physical being is at stake.
我的身体受到威胁。
Let's just leave it at that.
我们就这样吧。
SpongeBob,
you can tell me anything.
海绵宝宝，
你可以告诉我任何事情。
You've got to believe that.
你必须相信这一点。
Well... okay.
嗯……好吧。
But only if you promise
to keep it between us.
但前提是你答应了
把它保留在我们之间。
Of course.
当然。
Flats says
he's gonna kick my butt!
平底鞋说
他会踢我的屁股！
What?! There shall be
no butt-kicking
什么？！应有
没有踢屁股
in any class of mine.
在我的任何班级。
This is an adult program.
这是一个成人节目。
SpongeBob, just leave it to me.
海绵宝宝，交给我吧。
Aw, thanks, Mrs. Puff.
哦，谢谢，帕芙女士。
I knew I could count on you.
我知道我可以依靠你。
Have a nice lunch, SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝，午餐愉快吗？
Yes, Mrs. Puff.
是的，帕夫夫人。
Psst! SpongeBob!
嘘！海绵宝宝！
I talked to Flats for you.
我替你和弗拉茨谈过了。
I used your name.
我用了你的名字。
It was all a misunderstanding.
这一切都是一场误会。
You what?!
你什么？！
He was never going to
kick your butt at all.
他从来没有打算
踢你的屁股。
You see, SpongeBob,
Flats is from a town
你看，海绵宝宝，
Flats来自一个城镇
where "kicking someone's butt"
哪里“踢某人的屁股”
means that he wants
to be your friend
意味着他想要
成为你的朋友
and maybe play
也许可以玩
some sports with you
on weekends. and maybe play
和你一起做一些运动
周末。也许可以玩
some sports with you
on weekends.
和你一起做一些运动
周末。
I got diarrhea.
我腹泻了。
Huh?
啊？
Are you Flats's Dad?
你是弗拉茨的爸爸吗？
Why, yes, I am.
为什么，是的，我是。
Okay, see...
好吧，看...
I didn't know
where else to turn!
我不知道
还有哪里可以转！
Patrick couldn't help me
帕特里克无法帮助我
and Mrs. Puff
only made it worse!
和普芙夫人
只会让事情变得更糟！
I sit next to your son
Flats in school
我坐在你儿子旁边
学校里的公寓
and he is a fine boy and all
他是一个好男孩
and I don't want you
to take this the wrong way
我不想要你
采取错误的方式
but he wants to kick my butt.
但他想踢我的屁股。
Dad, what are you doing?
爸爸，你在做什么？
Uh, nothing, son.
呃，没什么，儿子。
What did I tell you
我告诉你什么了
about talking to strangers?
关于和陌生人说话？
Now he's going to kick mybutt.
现在他要踢我的屁股了。
Aah...!
啊啊……！
Out of my way! Out of my way!
别挡我的路！别挡我的路！
Can't you see
he's going to kick my butt?!
你看不到吗
他要踢我的屁股吗？
Hi there, young people!
嗨，年轻人！
Nice day today.
今天是美好的一天。
So you like kickin'
butts, do ya?
所以你喜欢踢
屁股，是吗？
Well, we'll show you, old man.
好吧，我们会告诉你，老伙计。
Okay, okay, I got to skip town!
好吧，好吧，我得逃城了！
Start a new life!
Live under an assumed name!
开始新的生活！
以化名生活！
BobPants SpongeSquare!
Yeah, that's good.
BobPants 海绵方形！
是的，那很好。
Grow a beard
and then shave it off....
留胡子
然后把它剃掉......
and live happily ever after.
从此过上幸福的生活。
Yeah, except you forgot the part
是的，除非你忘记了这个部分
where I kick your butt!
我在那里踢你的屁股！
Whoa...!
哇...！
Hey, Flats.
嘿，平底鞋。
You feeling better?
你感觉好些了吗？
Wh-wh-hat? Where am I?
什-什-帽子？我在哪里？
Why, you're in the hospital.
为什么，你在医院。
This young boy saved your life.
这个小男孩救了你的命。
He performed CPR
for five hours straight.
他进行了心肺复苏术
连续五个小时。
Yeah... they said you'd be okay
after the first few minutes
是的...他们说你会没事的
最初几分钟后
but I just wanted to be sure.
但我只是想确定一下。
Wow! I'm touched.
哇！我很感动。
I'll have to remember that
when I'm kicking your butt.
我必须记住这一点
当我踢你的屁股时。
Those flowers for me?
那些花是给我的？
Aah...!
啊啊……！
He's still gonna kick my butt!
他还是要踢我的屁股！
How many times do we have to
我们要经历多少次
teach you this lesson, old man?
教你这个教训吗，老家伙？
I love the young people.
我爱年轻人。
Aah...!
啊啊……！
Oh Gary! I'm too young
to have my butt kicked.
哦加里！我还太年轻
让我的屁股被踢。
There are so many things in life
that I haven't gotten to do!
生活中有很多事情
我还没来得及做！
Hang on...
I'll transfer your call.
坚持住...
我会转接你的电话。
Who is it?
是谁？
Aah...! Flats!
啊啊……！公寓！
It's butt-kicking time.
又到了踢屁股的时间了
Gary, there's something
I want you to know.
加里，有件事
我想让你知道。
But I'm too scared
to remember what it is.
但我太害怕了
记住它是什么。
Let's do it.
我们开始做吧。
Go away, Gary.
走开，加里。
I don't want you to see this,
it'll be ugly.
我不想让你看到这个
会很丑。
Are you ready?
你准备好了吗？
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Okay, I'm ready.
好的，我准备好了。
I said, I'm ready.
我说，我准备好了。
Huh?
啊？
Didn't you hear me?
你没听到我说话吗？
I said I'm ready.
我说我准备好了。
That tickled!
那个痒痒的！
Gary! I'm absorbing
his blows
加里！我正在吸收
他的打击
like I was made of some
kind of spongy material!
就像我是由一些组成的
一种海绵状材料！
And do you know what that means?
你知道这意味着什么吗？
I get to go to work tomorrow!
明天我还要去上班！
Do you have any sevens?
你有七人吗？
Flats? Are you okay?
公寓？你还好吗？
Do not cheer me, my
fellow adult classmates.
别为我欢呼，我的
成年同学。
Flats was the real victim here.
公寓是这里真正的受害者。
A victim of a society
社会的受害者
that's riding down
a violent road to nowhere...
那是下降的
一条通往无处可去的暴力之路……
a road I call "Violence Road."
一条我称之为“暴力之路”的路。
Sorry I'm late, class.
抱歉我迟到了，同学们。
I...
我...
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
I can't believe
you beat up a new student!
我不敢相信
你殴打了一个新学生！
I'm going to kick your butt!
我要踢你的屁股！
[Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
[字幕由THE赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
[Captioned byThe Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
[字幕由字幕中心提供
WGBH教育基金会]